Guide to the David Price Papers, 1960-2006 and undated RL.01048
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Campaign Office Files Record Group, 1982-1997 and undated
  - Audiovisual Materials Series, 1986-1996 and undated, 14 boxes
    - Videocassettes Subseries, 1986-1996 and undated
      - News Coverage and Television Appearances
        - Keeping in Touch
          - 1989
            - 32-36. Broadcast dates: Apr. 17, May 15, June 19, July 24, Aug. 28, Sept. 11, and 1990 Jan. 15. (Box AV-6)
              Tape 36 includes an interview with Terry Sanford [Audio quality is poor].
          - 1990
            - 37. Broadcast dates: Mar. 19 and Apr. 23. (Box AV-6)
              Tape contains part of each broadcast.
          - 1991
            - 38-42. Broadcast dates: Jan. 28, Feb. 18, Oct. 28, Nov. 11, and Dec. 16. (Box AV-6)
          - 1992
            - 43. Broadcast date: Jan. 20. (Box AV-6)
            - 44-46. Broadcast dates: Feb. 24, Mar. 30, and Apr. 27. (Box AV-7)
          - 1993
            - 47-56. Broadcast dates: Mar. 1, Apr. 5, May 3, July, Aug. 9, Sept., Oct. 4, Nov. 1, and Dec. 6. (Box AV-7)
              Tape 53 includes an interview of Jim Roberson, head of Research Triangle Park Foundation.
          - 1994
            - 57-59. Broadcast dates: Jan. 3, Feb., Mar. 7, and Apr. 11. (Box AV-7)
        - North Carolina Now (Box AV-8)
          - 1996
            - 60-61. Broadcast dates: Aug. 14 and undated. (Box AV-8)
              Tape 60 includes inteviews with Price and Fred Heineman [Video quality is poor].
        - North Carolina's Watch on Washington
          - 1987
            - 62. Broadcast date: Feb. (29:30) (Box AV-8)
              Talk show including reporting by Margaret Warner.
          - 1989
            - 63. Broadcast date: Feb. (Box AV-8)
              "Infant Mortality."
            - 64. Broadcast date: Mar. (29:30) (Box AV-8)
          - 1990
            - 65. Broadcast date: Apr. (28:00) (Box AV-8)
              "Health Care."
            - 66. Broadcast date: June (28:00) (Box AV-8)
              "Affordable Housing."
            - 67. Broadcast date: Dec. 11 (58:45) (Box AV-8)
            - 68. Broadcast date: Dec. 11 (58:45) (Box AV-8)
              "War: The Question - Taxes: The Certainty." Call-in show featuring Senators Terry Sanford, Jesse Helms, and Representatives Alex McMillan, Tim Valentine, and Martin Lancaster.
          - 1991
            - 69. (58:45) (Box AV-8)
              "In the Wake of War." Call-in show featuring Senator Sanford, and Representatives Neal, Coble, and Price.
            - 70. Broadcast date: Apr. 17 (58:45) (Box AV-8)
              "In the Wake of War." Hamilton Productions show hosted by John Hamilton with a panel including Rep. Price, Senator Sanford and others from North Carolina's Congressional delegation.
          - 1993
            - 71. Broadcast date: Mar. 2, (58:45) (Box AV-8)
              "Clinton's Agenda." Call-in show featuring Senator Faircloth and Representatives Ballenger, Price and Taylor
            - 72. Broadcast date: May 20 (58:45) (Box AV-8)
              "Health Care." Call-in show featuring Representatives Ballenger, Clayton, Price, and Valentine.
          - 1994 and undated
            - 73. Broadcast date: 1994 Apr. 27 (Box AV-8)
              "Cracking Down on Crime." Call-in show featuring Representatives Price, Coble, Watt, and Taylor.
            - 74. Broadcast date: Undated (Box AV-8)
              "Catastrophic Care."
        - Local News (Box AV-9)
          - 1986
            - 75. 1986 WTVD Election News (Box AV-9)
            - 76. 1986 WTVD News (Box AV-9)
              Rock Incident, WTVD news report about vandalism to Price opponent (Cobey) supporter's vehicle, and Price interview.
            - 77. 1986 Forum, Cobey-Price, WPTF? (Box AV-9)
              Cobey/Price campaign debate hosted by Terry Thill.
            - 78. CBS, 1986 Oct. 29, Channel 5, 1986 Oct. 30 (Box AV-9)
              Saputo, Rally, Channel 11 Interview.
            - 79. 1986 Election Night News (Box AV-9)
          - 1990
            - 80. Reports on Congressman Price, 1990 June (Box AV-9)
              Appearances by and news on Price (WRAL, WBTV, and WTVD).
            - 81. Reports on Congressman Price, 1990 June-July (Box AV-9)
              Seven local broadcast news reports concerning Price.
            - 82. Reports on Congressman Price, week of 1990 Sept. 7-13 (Box AV-9)
              Three local broadcast news reports concerning Price.
            - 83. Reports on Congressman Price received 1990 Sept. 14-20 (Box AV-9)
              One local broadcast news report concerning Price (WTVD).
            - 84. Reports on Congressman Price received during week of 1990 Sept. 26-Oct. 1 (Box AV-9)
              One local broadcast news report concerning Price (WRAL).
            - 85. Reports on Congressman Price, 1990 Oct. 5-14 (Box AV-9)
            - 86. Reports on Congressman Price received during week of 1990 Oct. 15-Oct. 25 (Box AV-9)
              Two local broadcast news reports concerning Price (WTVD and WPTF).
            - 87. Reports on Congressman Price, 1990 Oct. 26-Nov. 12 (Box AV-9)
              Compilation of broadcast news reports including live coverage of Price win (WTVD, WPTF, and WRAL).
            - 88. NEXRAD Reports, WRAL-TV, 1990 Nov. 16, Nov. 28, and Nov. 29 (Box AV-9)
              News coverage of Next-Generation Weather Radar (Doppler) system.
          - 1994
            - 89. Fox 22 News, 1994 May (Box AV-9)
              News report with statements from both Price and Heineman; reporting on other campaigns; miscellaneous television programming; a similar news report on Heineman/Price; and additional unrelated television programming.
          - 1996 and undated
            - 90. Price for Congress 1996, AARP (Box AV-10)
              WRAL News segment on panel discussion with speakers Price and opponent Heineman held by AARP [American Association of Retired Persons] followed by unrelated television programming.
            - 91. To Have and Have Not (Box AV-10)
              Fox 22 News report on national campaigns of 1996 including the Heineman/Price campaigns; an ABC local Channel 11 report on Price; the Bush-Dole presidential debate, unrelated television programming; and then part of a Paul Wellstone debate (1996, Minnesota Senate race).
            - 92. Campaign Video Clips and Fetzer Spots (Box AV-10)
              Fetzer campaign commercials; and news reports on Price efforts and campaign including one on Fetzer/Price debate. [Video quality is poor.]
            - 93. Congressman David Price, Aug. (Box AV-10)
              News coverage (WTVD, WPTF, et al.) with comments from Price on economy in light of possible Iraq war.
        - Other
          - 1986
            - 94. WUNC Campaign Forum, 1986 (Box AV-10)
              Show hosted by Richard Hatch featuring Price and opponent Bill Cobey.
          - 1987
            - 95. Rep. Walter Jones, "The U.S. Congress and You," 1987 Feb. 6 (Box AV-10)
              Show on the U.S. Congress sponsored by Burroughs Wellcome, featuring Walter Jones and Howard K. Smith.
          - 1988
            - 96. CNN's Moneyline, 1988 Feb. 24 (Box AV-10)
              Home Equity Disclosure Markup, Rep. David Price.
            - 97. USTA, Congressional PSA's: Link Up America, Rep. David E. Price, NTSC 525, DUB. 1988 Mar. (Box AV-10)
              Clip about Link Up America project.
            - 98. David Price-HR 3011, Home Equity-C-SPAN, 1988 June 20 (Box AV-10)
              This is only copy of House Home Equity Speech Footage of Frank Annunzio and Price speaking on House floor.
            - 99. DP-Speech before Democratic Convention, 1988 July 21, Atlanta (Box AV-10)
              C-SPAN footage of Democratic Convention including Price speech mentioning his Home Equity Loan Act.
            - 100. MacNeil-Lehrer, 1988 (Box AV-10)
              Discussion of superdelegates for Democratic Convention. CNN coverage featuring comment by Price.
            - 101. D.P. Superdelegate, CNN Itvw. (Box AV-10)
              CNN show Inside Politics '88, on Jesse Jackson and superdelegates, including brief clip of Price.
          - 1989
            - 102. Washington Connection, 1989 May 4 (Box AV-10)
              Congressmen Walter Jones, Tim Valentine, and David Price, N.C. Agency for Public Telecommunications Call-in show hosted by Leila Tveat with guests Price, Valentine, and Jones.
          - 1990
            - 103. WUNC TV Interview, 1990 Oct. 21; Carrington Taxes ad. 1990 Oct. 15; Carrington SandL/Captiva Island ad, 1990 Oct. 21 Carrington campaign ad (Box AV-10)
              WUNC show hosted by Richard Hatch with interviews of Price and Carrington; television programming and additional Carrington ad. [Video quality is poor].
            - 104. WFMY/Greensboro Chamber joint appearance, Price/Carrington, 1990 Oct. 30 (Box AV-10)
              GTCC Candidates Forum; local news story on George Bush (The Good Morning Show) with national show cut-in (CBS) including a segment on the coming election; segment on Gantt/Helms Senate (North Carolina) race; Gantt/Helms campaign ads and more of the shows; Steve Neal campaign ad; and Carrington/Price ads.
          - 1991
            - 105. Chapel Hill Meeting, 1991 Jan. 11 (Box AV-10)
              America Tonight, show broadcast from Chapel Hill, NC on the Iraq War.
            - 106. Rep. Perking [sic] C. with Rep. Price D., 1991 Sept. 12 (Box AV-11)
              Edition of Washington Edition with Chris Perkins.
            - 107. Washington Connection, 1991 Oct. 10 (Box AV-11)
              Call-in show hosted by Leila Tveat with Price and others.
          - 1992
            - 108. Community View (dub), 1992 June (Box AV-11)
              Show hosted by Martin Sheridan featuring Price and opponent Vicky Rothrock Goudie.
            - 109. Participate in Tomorrow, PAC Solicitation, 10:25, 1992 June (Box AV-11)
              Contains short appearances by North Carolina and South Carolina politicians including Price.
            - 110. Rep. Perkins with Rep. Price, 1992 July 8 (Box AV-11)
              Show titled Washington Edition with Chris Perkins, interview of Price.
            - 111. WUNC Debate, 1992 Sept. 22 (Box AV-11)
              Clip of Price and other candidates responding to questions. [Video quality is poor].
          - 1993
            - 112. Price: March Madness 1-min., 1993 Mar. 31 (Box AV-11)
              Several House floor speeches.
            - 113. Rep. David Price Address to TC Squared Building Dedication, 1993 Oct. (Box AV-11)
            - 114. NAFTA Debate: Floor Statement, 1993 Nov. 17 (Box AV-11)
              Various speakers on House floor discussing NAFTA [North American Free Trade Agreement].
          - 1994
            - 115. Health Care [et al.?], 1 min., 1994 Feb. 3 (Box AV-11)
              Price's House floor speeches.
            - 116. The Raleigh Rescue Mission, Copyright 1994, 11:35 (Box AV-11)
          - 1996 and undated
            - 117. DP on Fox AARP Debate (Box AV-11)
              Fragments of a WETA fundraiser and Paul Wellstone debate (1996 Senate campaign (Minn.)); a local Fox News story very similar to news report on Tape 1 above [6:00 and 11:00 reports?]; more of the Wellstone debate, Book Talk, This Week with David Brinkley, the WETA fundraiser; and unrelated television programming.
            - 118. Bill Bagley, Cablevision, Community View, July, Congressman David Price (Box AV-11)
            - 119. CNN Profiles in Congress, Rep. David Price (Box AV-11)
            - 120. C-SPAN: Nixon Library Dedication (Box AV-11)
              C-SPAN coverage of library dedication in Yorba Linda, Calif.
            - 121. The U.S. Congress and You, Representative David Price, Sponsored by North Carolina State University. (Box AV-11)
      - Miscellaneous Format Videocassettes
        Two videocassettes in non-VHS formats. Have not been viewed.
        - Help 1, undated Beta L-750 videocassette (Box AV-12)
        - David Price for Congress, 1987 Feb. 26. U-matic videocassette (Box AV-12)
    - Videotapes (original copies), undated
      - Price/Difference-Revised, DP30-155-4R, (:30) / Shooters, Inc., Suite 302, 2428 Route 38, Cherry Hill, NJ 08002, 609/482-9090 (one-inch video tape), 4 reels (Box AV-13)
- Additions to the collection, 15 boxes
  Additional accessions that have not been integrated into the existing collection are described in the boxlists below.
  All additions are closed to research except by donor permission.
  - Accession (2010-0219), 1987-2004
    Accession 2010-0219 consists of 10 boxes with materials from Price's 1996, 1998, 2000, 2002, and 2004 campaigns. The 1996 materials consists largely of fundraising files. The 1998-2004 campaigns also include campaign manager files, media and press files, and fundraising files. Materials include candidate surveys, forums, issue papers, media spots, and oppenent information.
    Accession 2010-0219 included 8 3.5 floppy disks that have been removed from the collection and migrated to Duke's Electronic Records server. Please contact Research Services for access to this material.
    ACCESS IS RESTRICTED to this portion of the collection. Please consult Research Services before requesting this material.
    - Fundraising, 1996 (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      Materials within this subseries date from 1996 unless otherwise noted.
      - National Taxpayers Union, 1994 (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Individual contributors (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Individual contributors, further follow-up (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Group A (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Group B (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Group C (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Group D (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - New calls (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Pending calls (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Calls with letters out (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Conpleted contracts (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - David Price's reading file (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Contracts, 2 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Washington event, 1996 March 27 (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Other candidates' financial reports and Federal Elections Commissions report, 2 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Peacock Town/Gown Party, 1996 Oct 3 (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Miscellaneous scheduling and Thank You notes (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Spring/Fall schedule for 1996 campaign (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Scheduling and organization trips (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Debates/forum invitations (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - David Price Calendar of Events, 2 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Adams/Spearman fundraiser, 1995 (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Pledge for Price fundraiser, 1996 (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Indian American money (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Chinese American money (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Miscellaneous letters and articles (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Pledge for Price-Fearrington checks (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Non-labor political action committees contributions (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Labor political action committees contributions (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Phoning lists (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
      - Coxer-Burns Garden Party (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
    - Legislative Record Book II: 1st Session of the 105th Congress, 1997 (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
    - Campaign, 1998
      Additional materials from the 1998 campaign are in the Audio and Video Recordings subseries, Boxes 11 and 12.
      - Campaign Manager files, 1998
        - ADM Cross-tabulation count report (Voter File) (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
        - Administration
          - Cary Office Lease (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
          - Computer information (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
          - Adams Consulting (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
          - Bell South (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
          - Pager service (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
          - Office Max (Box Acc. 10/219: 1)
        - Field (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Contact List (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Labor contacts (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Primary congratulations letters (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Phone program/Tyson (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - NC coordinated campaign (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Targeting
          - Past election results (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - 1998 primary results (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - District Profiles
          - Zip Code list (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Chatham County
          - Chatham Precinct organization (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Durham County
          - Durham background (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Orange County
          - Southern Orange Black Caucus (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Orange County Democratic Party (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - David Price Precinct Chair (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Orange County Committee (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Daily Tar Heel advertisement (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Wake County
          - Wake County Precinct Organization (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Finance
          - Budgets: 1992, 1994, 1996 (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Budget 1998 (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Finance 1998 (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Solicitation letter, 1998 June (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Thank you letters, 1998, 3 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Fundraising letter, 1998 Sept. (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Small Donor letter, 1998 Aug. (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Thank you letter, 1998 Sept. 23 (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Bowles event (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Ann Richards fundraising letter (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - FEC Reports
          - Candidate filing No. 2, 1998 (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - FEC Reports, 1998, 6 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Materials
          - Master Issue Papers, 1996 (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Town Hall document (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Campaign bio (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Push card (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Website (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Push card truth test (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Congressional bio (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Congressional newsletter, 1998 June (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Press
          - Press plan (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Letters to the editor (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Roberg/Gingrich release, 1998 July (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Polling
          - WTVD Polls, 2 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - March 1998 (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - September 1998 (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - October Tracks 1-3, 3 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Mail
          - Mail, 1996 (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Voter file information (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - CPG contract (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Mail piece No. 1: Education (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Direct mail plan (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Radio
          - Radio No. 1: M&S (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Hillary/DCCC Radio Ad (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Media/Television
          - Shorr and Associations (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - TV Buys (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Cable Information (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Television scripts, 2 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - TV production, 2 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Film shoots, 2 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Roberg Miscellaneous
          - Debate/Spending limits letter (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Blumenthal letter (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Correspondence, 1998 (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Liberal, Dome article (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - NFIB endorsement (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
        - Roberg FEC Reports
          - Statement of organization (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Financial Disclosure Reports, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - FEC Reports, 1997-1998, 3 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - Pre-primary, 1998 Aug. 31 (Box Acc. 10/219: 2)
          - 48 Hour reports, pre-primary, 1998 (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - FEC Reports, 1998, 2 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - FEC Problems and Summaries (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Roberg Finance
          - Boehner and Gingrich (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Gingrich event (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Boehner event (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Fundraising letter, 1998 Jan. 10 (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Gingrich transcript (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Walter Jones event (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Burr/Joyner event (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Forbes event (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Roberg Materials
          - Campaign material (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Website (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Bio (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Roberg Message Delivery
          - Clinton Resign Release (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Campaign schedules (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Newsletters (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Duke Republicans (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Foundation for Voter Information, Primary 1998 (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - UNC Radio (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Roberg Issues
          - Grassroots North Carolina speech (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Republican fact sheet (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Right to Work (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Roberg Media: Radio
          - Scripts, Primary (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Buy, Primary (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - WSHA Interview, 1998 July 27 (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Script, Nice Guy spot (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Buy, 1998 Aug. 1 (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot, Education (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot No. 4, Clinton Resign (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot No. 5, Tom Roberg on... (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot No. 6, Resignation Revised (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot No. 7, 90 Percent and a Smile (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Roberg Media: Television
          - Time Buy Summaries (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Questions to ask Roberg (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot No. 1, Charts (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot No. 2, Flag (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot No. 3, Education/Clinton (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot No. 4, Clinton Resign (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot No. 5, Clinton Resign 2 (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot No. 6, Taxes (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Spot No. 7, Taxes and Social Security (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Cable TV Buy, 1998 Aug., 2 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Roberg Research
          - Los Angeles County research (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Quotes (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Research profile (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Wake research (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - McCorkle Search (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Tom Roberg Show, 1998, 3 folders (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Roberg transcripts (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Miscellaneous Files, 1996
          - Campaign plan (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Fundraising memo/strategies (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Field plan (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - Fundraising schedules (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
          - District profile (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - DP Mail
          - Voter mail (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
      - Finance, 1998
        - Finance 1998 (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - David's invites (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Birthday celebration, IRR (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Bowler events (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Campbell (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - DC BBQ (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Fiesta (Edwards) (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Hillsborough (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - PAC reception (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Page-Walker reception (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Pavao reception (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - Pinsky-Adelmans reception (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)
        - UNC-Peacock reception (Box Acc. 10/219: 3)